Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kajal-verma-45210149 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Recruiting
Sourcing
Benefits Negotiation

Kajal Verma

Campus Recruiter at American Express

Bengaluru Rural

Summary

I am University Hiring Recruiter with overall 9 years of knowledge in talent acquisitions & specialize in university/campus hiring. As a University Recruiter I program manage end to end hiring cycle for Amex Technology. Stakeholder management is one of my greatest strengths.

I believe in growth mindset which always helps me think on my feet and helps me to deal with any difficult situation.

Experience

American Express
Campus Recruiter - Technology
July 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)
Bengaluru Area, India

Microsoft
Campus Recruiter
November 2015 - Present (4 years 10 months)
Bengaluru Area, India

Goldman Sachs Staffing Specialist - Campus Asia July 2013 - July 2015 (2 years 1 month) bangalore

Tesco PLC HR - Recruiter (Online Recruitment) August 2010 - April 2012 (1 year 9 months) Bangalore

Convergeon HR - Recruiter April 2008 - April 2009 (1 year 1 month)

Bangalore

- Matching prospective profiles from company database to evaluate skill sets, with client brief.
- Maintaining offer letter tracker and reports.
- Short listing of the selected candidates using personal and telephonic interviews.
- Updating the company's candidate database.
- Network and data mining of job portals.
- Screening of resumes from various portals and initiation of background verification for new joiners.
- To ensure offer letter being issued immediately on receipt of hire and to ensure HR briefing and documentation to new joiners.

Education

Symbiosis Institute of Management Studies
PGDHRM, Human Resources Management and Services · (2018 - 2020)

Rajiv Gandhi Collage
Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com.), Business/Managerial
Economics · (2006 - 2009)

St Michaels

12th, Commerce · (2002 - 2006)